Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Public Performances, 1965-1997, Jun 25, 1965-Feb 22, 1997
  - "Sessions Miltown 1984." A variety of sessions featuring musicians Noel Hill (concertina), Tony Linnane (fiddle), Tony McMahon (accordion) in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare and a private recording of Frank Harte singing several songs. (Length: 00:50:00). aiamm999C, Jul, 1984; aiamm999C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Willie Clancy Week. Moloney lecture interspersed with musical examples in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare recorded for the Long Note radio program, "Banjo Music." (Length: 00:45:00). aiamm998C, Jul, 1984; aiamm998C (Box 40, Box 26)
  - Green Fields of America. Second half of a concert performance. Musicians include: Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), James Keane (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle). Liz Carroll plays tunes for O'Sullivan at the end. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1000C, Oct 26, 1984; aiamm1000C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Scottsdale, AZ. Musicians: Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (flute, whistle, concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny Golden (dancing), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals). (Four CDs – Total length: 02:09:25) aiamm167C, 168C, Oct 28, 1984; aiamm167C, aiamm168C (Box 10, Box 34, Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in New Orleans, LA. Musicians: Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (flute, whistle, concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny Golden (dancing), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals). (Three CDs – Total length: 01:59:07) aiamm169C, 170C, Nov 2, 1984; aiamm169C, aiamm170C (Box 34, Box 10, Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Memphis, TN. Musicians: Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (flute, whistle, concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny Golden (dancing), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals). (One CD – Length: 00:44:57) aiamm136R, Nov 3, 1984; aiamm136R (Box 9, Box 31, Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Green Fields of America. Second half of a concert performance in Memphis, TN. Musicians include: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), James Keane (accordion) (Length:01:00:00) aiamm1001C, Nov 3, 1984; aiamm1001C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Nashville, TN. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals). aiamm1002C, Nov 4, 1984; aiamm1002C (Box 54, Box 26)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Nashville, TN. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals). aiamm1431C, Nov 4, 1984; aiamm1431C (Box 44, Box 70)
  - "Mick et. al. - Tucson, AZ - 1st set." aiamm1003C, Feb 9, 1985; aiamm1003C (Box 54, Box 27)
  - Folk Music with Gene Shay. Radio program recorded by Gene Shay and broadcast on either WXPN-FM or WHYY-FM in Philadelphia, PA. Traditional music and interview with Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin, guitar, vocals), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes). (One CD – Length: 00:18:16) aiamm274C, Mar, 1985; aiamm274C (Box 7, Folder 8, Box 12, Box 34)
  - Mick Moloney and Friends. St. Patrick's week concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, vocals), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes). (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm1004C, Mar, 1985; aiamm1004C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), O'Sullivan, Jerry (uilleann pipes),Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Muted, hissy concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 00:45:00). aiamm1005C, Mar 16, 1985; aiamm1005C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo, Uruguay - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1006C, Apr 12, 1985; aiamm1006C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo, Uruguay - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1007C, Apr 12, 1985; aiamm1007C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Paysendu, Uruguay - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1008C, Apr 13, 1985; aiamm1008C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Paysendu, Uruguay - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1009C, Apr 13, 1985; aiamm1009C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Montevideo, Uruguay - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1010C, Apr 15, 1985; aiamm1010C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Montevideo, Uruguay - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1011C, Apr 15, 1985; aiamm1011C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in La Paz, Bolivia - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1012C, Apr 18, 1985; aiamm1012C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in La Paz, Bolivia - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:20:00) aiamm1013C, Apr 18, 1985; aiamm1013C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santa Cruz, Bolivia. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1014C, Apr 19, 1985; aiamm1014C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santa Cruz, Bolivia. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1015C, Apr 19, 1985; aiamm1015C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cochabamba, Bolivia - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1016C, Apr 21, 1985; aiamm1016C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cochabamba, Bolivia - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1017C, Apr 21, 1985; aiamm1017C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in La Paz, Bolivia. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1018C, Apr 22, 1985; aiamm1018C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Guayaquil, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1019C, Apr 25, 1985; aiamm1019C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Guayaquil, Ecuador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1020C, Apr 26, 1985; aiamm1020C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Guayaquil, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1021C, Apr 26, 1985; aiamm1021C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cuenco, Equador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1022C, Apr 29, 1985; aiamm1022C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cuenco, Equador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1023C, Apr 29, 1985; aiamm1023C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1024C, May 1, 1985; aiamm1024C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1025C, May 1, 1985; aiamm1025C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1029C, May 2, 1985; aiamm1029C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1030C, May 2, 1985; aiamm1030C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:41:50) aiamm202C, May 4, 1985; aiamm202C (Box 7, Folder 9, Box 11, Box 34)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Casa Grande Reception, Managua, Nicaragua - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1031C, May 4, 1985; aiamm1031C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Casa Grande Reception, Managua, Nicaragua - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1032C, May 4, 1985; aiamm1032C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance; Managua, Nicaragua: "Ruins of the Gran Hotel." aiamm1254C, May 5, 1985; aiamm1254C (Box 67, Box 44)
  - Reavy Concert Tape 1. Concert performance by Joe Reavy featuring poetry and songs from Mary Touque, Mike McKinley, Dennis Heron, Dennis Boone, Roy Rogers and music composed by Ed and Joe Reavy. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1034C, May 4, 1985; aiamm1034C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Reavy Concert Tape 2. Concert performance by Joe Reavy featuring poetry and songs from Mary Touque, Mike McKinley, Dennis Heron, Dennis Boone, Roy Rogers and music composed by Ed and Joe Reavy. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1035C, May 4, 1985; aiamm1035C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:51:34) aiamm203C, May 5, 1985; aiamm203C (Box 7, Folder 10, Box 11, Box 34)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:51:06) aiamm204C, May 6, 1985; aiamm204C (Box 11, Box 7, Folder 11, Box 34)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance: Ruins of The Grand Hotel; Managua, Nicaragua (Tape 1). aiamm1397C, May 6, 1985; aiamm1397C (Box 44, Box 70)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. Concert performance at the ruins of the Grand Hotel (Casa Grande) in Managua, Nicaragua. Susie Goff and the Green Grass Cloggers, Mick Moloney (mandolin) and Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals) perform as part of the South American tour of Irish and Appalachian musicians for the United States Information Agency. (One CD – Length: 00:40:07) aiamm205C, May 7, 1985; aiamm205C (Box 34, Box 11, Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic. aiamm1261C, May 10, 1985; aiamm1261C (Box 68, Box 44)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1026C, May 10, 1985; aiamm1026C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1027C, May 11, 1985; aiamm1027C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dom. Rep., Tape 2. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1028C, May 11, 1985; aiamm1028C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Augusta Irish Week Concert: First Set (Moloney, Mick; O'Connell, Robbie; Keane, Jimmy; Briley, Rosalyn; Harte, Frank; Carroll, Liz; McComiskey, Billy; Britton, Tim; Golden, Donny). aiamm1390C, Jul 29, 1985; aiamm1390C (Box 66, Box 44)
  - Augusta Irish Week Concert: Second Set aiamm1310C, Jul 29, 1985; aiamm1310C (Box 65, Box 44)
  - Augusta Irish Week Panel: "The Irish Tradition in America" (1 of 2) aiamm1302C, Jul 31, 1985; aiamm1302C (Box 44, Box 65)
  - Ennis Concert. Second half of a concert performance in Ennis, Co. Clare featuring the Ormond Ceili Band led by Paddy O'Brien (accordion), Mary McNamara (concertina), Jim Curry, Paddy Murphy (concertina), Peadar O'Loughlin (fiddle). (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1036C, Jul, 1985; aiamm1036C (Box 54, Box 26)
  - Miltown Malbay. Fragments of concert performances in Co. Clare. (Length: 00:20:00) aiamm1037C, Jul, 1985; aiamm1037C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Sessions in Miltown. Sessions in Co. Clare with Jimmy Keane (accordion), Moloney (banjo). (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1038C, Jul, 1985; aiamm1038C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - "Last Evening of Tour Talent Show and Session." aiamm1346C, Aug 12, 1985; aiamm1346C (Box 71, Box 44)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Milwaukee, WI. Musicians: Timmy Britton (uilleann pipes), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, flute), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (button accordion), Donny and Eileen Golden (dancing), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals), Jimmy Keane (piano accordion), James Keane, Sr. (sean nos singer). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:17:26) aiamm135R, Aug, 1985; aiamm135R (Box 9, Box 31, Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Moloney, Mick (banjo, mandolin, vocals), Keane, Jimmy (piano accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals), Carroll, Liz (fiddle), Bernstein, Ira (dancing). Concert performance at the Wheatland Music Festival, Remus, MI. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:32:10) aiamm298C, Sep, 1985; aiamm298C (Box 12, Box 34, Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, banjo), Keane, James (accordion), Egan, Seamus (mandolin, flute, mandolin) Concert performance in Bethlehem, PA. (probably at Godfrey Daniels). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:31:48) aiamm284C, Dec 28, 1985; aiamm284C (Box 7, Folder 15, Box 34, Box 12)
  - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Brazzaville. (Length: 00:40:00) aiamm1033C, 1985; aiamm1033C (Box 60, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), Carroll, Liz (fiddle), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) - End of an echoey concert performance in Laytonville, CA. (Length: 00:20:00) aiamm1039C, 1985; aiamm1039C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Mount Airy: Bands of Dance Contest. aiamm1411C, 1985; aiamm1411C (Box 44, Box 70)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance in the Barn at University of California, Riverside. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1040C, Jan, 1986; aiamm1040C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance in Pittsburgh, PA. (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm1041C, Feb 20, 1986; aiamm1041C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Mick Moloney and Friends. St. Patrick's Day concert performance at Gaston Hall, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Regan Wick (dance). (Length:01:00:00). aiamm1042C, Mar 17, 1986; aiamm1042C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Sanchez, Emmanuel: Stetson Residency and Spring Feis. aiamm1272C, May 12, 1986; aiamm1272C (Box 44, Box 68)
  - Sanchez, Emmanuel: Stetson Residency and Spring Feis. aiamm1427C, May 12, 1986; aiamm1427C (Box 74, Box 44)
  - Session at Moloney's. Quiet session with Mairtin O'Connor (accordion), Dolores Keane (whistle), John Faulkner (mandolin, bouzouki), unidentified flute in Philadelphia, PA., with dog. (Length: 00:50:00). aiamm1043C, May 19, 1986; aiamm1043C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Egan, Siobhan (fiddle) Interview with Earle Hitchener on WFDU, Fairleigh Dickinson University, Madison, NJ. Sibling musicians promote the album, Seamus Egan. Broadcast Jul 12, 1986. (Length: 00:20:00). aiamm1044C, Jun 14, 1986; aiamm1044C (Box 40, Box 26)
  - Central Hotel, Miltown. Session in Co. Clare labeled "Copy S. Egan." (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1236C, Jul, 1986; aiamm1236C (Box 26, Box 64)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, mandolin), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at the Painted Bride Arts Center, Philadelphia, PA. (Length:00:40:00) aiamm1045C, Oct 21, 1986; aiamm1045C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Folk Artists in the Schools (FAIS): Italian. aiamm1286C, 1986; aiamm1286C (Box 44, Box 72)
  - "Irish Fair, Set 1." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1208C, 1986; aiamm1208C (Box 26, Box 64)
  - "Irish Fair, Set 2." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1209C, 1986; aiamm1209C (Box 64, Box 26)
  - "Irish Fair, Sunday - 1st Set - 3 of 4, 4 of 4." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1210C, 1986; aiamm1210C (Box 26, Box 64)
  - "Irish Fair, Last Set, Last Songs, Sun." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 00:10:00) aiamm1211C, 1986; aiamm1211C (Box 64, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, mandolin, banjo), Keane, James (accordion), Egan, Seamus (mandolin, flute, whistle, uilleann pipes, banjo). Concert performance at the Turning Point, Piermont, NY. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:25:43) aiamm278C, Mar 1, 1987; aiamm278C (Box 12, Box 34, Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, mandolin), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 0:50:00). aiamm1046C, Mar 14, 1987; aiamm1046C (Box 40, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, mandolin), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 01:30:00). aiamm1047C, Mar 1987; aiamm1047C (Box 40, Box 26)
  - "Moloney, O'Connell, Keane - Minneapolis." aiamm1048C, May 29, 1987; aiamm1048C (Box 55, Box 27)
  - International Village Fair: Neighbor's Complaint; Fiddle Puppets. aiamm1465C, Jul 25, 1987; aiamm1465C (Box 45, Box 69)
  - International Village Fair: Arts of Celebration Workshop: Terence Cameron (drummer), The Fabulous Mummers, Glen Harrison (presenter) (Stage II). aiamm1414C, Jul 26, 1987; aiamm1414C (Box 70, Box 44)
  - International Village Fair: Celtic and Andean Flutes. Flute workshop in Philadelphia, PA, moderated by Tim Britton comparing Celtic and Andean flutes and flute-playing. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1049C, Jul 26, 1987; aiamm1049C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - International Village Fair: O'Donnell & McCafferty Workshop. Workshop performances in Philadelphia, PA. Side A: Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) introduces duets featuring himself and James McCafferty (piano) (15 minutes) followed by Swedish music; Side B: O'Donnell and McCafferty duets (30 minutes) followed by Old-time music. (Total length: 00:45:00) aiamm1050C, Jul 27, 1987; aiamm1050C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - International Village Fair: Sally Peterson on Hmong Culture, Pang Xiang on Needlework, Chiq Kerlor on Baskets; Fiddle Puppets International Dance (Stage 2) aiamm1296C, Jul 27, 1987; aiamm1296C (Box 65, Box 44)
  - International Village Fair: Workshop performances in Philadelphia, PA. Side A: Afternoon Cape Breton workshop with Maybelle Chisolm McQueen, Buddy MacMaster, David MacIsaacs, John Pellerin; Side B: Wind workshop with Semus Egan (flute)and Tim Britton (uilleann pipes) (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1051C, Jul 28, 1987; aiamm1051C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - International Village Fair: Crafting Nature into Art (Glenn Hinson), Storytelling (Jim Albertson). aiamm1297C, Jul 29, 1987; aiamm1297C (Box 44, Box 66)
  - International Village Fair: Fiddle Puppets, Sang-Won Park. aiamm1374C, Jul 28, 1987; aiamm1374C (Box 73, Box 44)
  - International Village Fair: Tradition and Change; Hmong Needlework; Fiddle Puppets International Dance (Men Only) (Stage 2). aiamm1301C, Jul 29, 1987; aiamm1301C (Box 44, Box 69)
  - Moloney, Mick (banjo, mandolin, vocals), Keane, Jimmy (piano accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals). Concert performance at the Cuyahoga Valley Festival in the Cuyahoga Valley National Recreation Area near Cleveland, OH. recorded by WKSU – FM. (One CD – Length: 00:41:29) aiamm330C, Sep 19, 1987; aiamm330C (Box 34, Box 7, Folder 17, Box 13)
  - Cherish the Ladies. Concert performance in Geneva, NY. Musicians: Joanie Madden (flute, whistle), Mary Coogan (guitar), Maureen Doherty (flute, accordion, whistle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Siobhan Egan (fiddle, whistle), Bridget Fitzgerald (vocals), Eileen Golden, Mairead Powell, Maureen Kennelly (dancers). (Three CDs – Total Length: 01:41:05) aiamm206, 207C, Oct 10, 1987; aiamm206, aiamm207C (Box 7, Folder 18, Box 11, Box 34)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance at UC Santa Barbara, CA. Musicians include: Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Jimmy Keane (accordion). (Length: 00:20:00) aiamm1052C, Oct 20, 1987; aiamm1052C (Box 59, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, James (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Concert performance at "Morley's." (Length: 01:20:00) aiamm1053C, Nov 23, 1987; aiamm1053C (Box 26, Box 59)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Interview in Los Angeles for Folk Scene, a Pacifica radio show hosted by Howard Larman. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1054C, circa 1987; aiamm1054C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Ivers, Eileen (fiddle) Concert performance at the Somerville Theater, Somerville, MA. (Length: 00:20:00). aiamm1055C, Jan 29, 1988; aiamm1055C (Box 40, Box 26)
  - Connolly, Seamus (fiddle), Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo). Concert performance in Convent Station, NJ. (Part one) (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1056C, Feb 13, 1988; aiamm1056C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Connolly, Seamus (fiddle), Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo). Concert performance in Convent Station, NJ. (Part two) (Length: 01:10:00) aiamm1057C, Feb 13, 1988; aiamm1057C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Fresh Air. Brief interview and performance by Moloney on the Philadelphia radio show hosted by Terri Gross. (Length: 00:05:00). aiamm1058C, Feb 19, 1988; aiamm1058C (Box 26, Box 55)
  - Train to Sligo (group) Concert performance of the California band featuring songwriter Thom Moore, opening for the Grateful Dead. Not Moloney's recording. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm1059C, Mar 17, 1988; aiamm1059C (Box 26, Box 79)
  - Cherish the Ladies. Concert performance at Brookdale Community College in Lincroft, NJ. Musicians: Joanie Madden (flute, whistle), Mary Coogan (guitar), Maureen Doherty (flute, accordion, whistle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Siobhan Egan (fiddle, whistle), Bridget Fitzgerald (sean nos singer), Eileen Golden, Mairead Powell, Maureen Kennelly (dancers) and Cathie [Ryan] Henry (vocals) in her first appearance with the group. (Three CDs – Total Length: 01:48:24 ) aiamm208C, 209C, Mar 20, 1988; aiamm208C, aiamm209C (Box 7, Folder 19, Box 34, Box 11)